

# **Summary**

As an experienced developer who is a core part of my project teams. I deliver high quality codes which meet or exceed the requirements. I help you solve problems with web & mobile app development, performance improvements, bug fixing, and even more. My soft skills also guarantee me to output the maximum productivity as well as to support teammates when they need help.

# **Employment**

Accenture Toronto June 2021 to Current

Application Developer Full Stack

- Implement and deliver story features of mobile application in an agile sprint
- framework, with the unit test coverage reaching 90%. • Improve the performance of a sub-system by 75% in its loading time via code refactoring and optimization.
- Maintain production apps, fix defects, and expand existing features.

Revature Toronto Mar. 2021 to Current Full Stack Developer

- Implement story features on banking project and reimbursement system, with 15% of functionalities exceeding the user expectation.
- Contribute backend codes to bug bounty board application, support on debugging, and unit testing.

North York Somoplay Software developer May 2020 to Dec. 2020

- Develop website landing page, admin management portal, and email template system.
- Trouble-shoot issues on data rendering, website optimization, and fix defects.

Torneo Toronto **Company Collaborator** Feb. 2019 to Mar. 2020

- Implement stand-alone blog module components, and its content editing system.
- Develop website responsive sign-in/register page, and mobile navigation component.

# **Projects**

**Bug Bounty V1** Mar. 2021 to June 2021

Bug Bounty is an application designed for business and development level users to report and track bugs on the internal applications used in Revature.

Mar. 2021 to June 2021 Simple Trader

Simple Trader is an online marketplace platform that provides a convenient way for people to buy and sell things.

### **Expense Reimbursement System**

Mar. 2021 to Apr. 2021

Expense Reimbursement System manages the process of reimbursing employees for expenses incurred during company time.

Feb. 2019 to Mar. 2019 **Avoid The Bricks** 

HTML5 game developed with jQuery where player avoids the falling bricks and survive as long as possible.

## **Contact**

**☑** guannanlv@gmail.com

https://glv1at118.github.io/guannanportfolio-terminal/

905-519-2561

### **Education**

University of Toronto

Sept. 2016 to June

Master's Degree Engineering 2018

# Skills

### **BACK END & DATABASE**

lava FF

**Spring Framework** 

Hibernate

C#

**NET Core** 

**Entity Framework Core** 

Node.js

**Express** 

**PostgreSQL** 

Microsoft SQL Server

MongoDB

Kinvey

RabbitMQ

### FRONT END & MOBILE

**Javascript** 

Typescript

React

Angular

Vue

iOuerv

Ionic Framework

PrimeNG

**Bootstrap** 

### **DEVOPS & MISC**

AWS

Azure

Git

Docker

Linux